# **Abhishek Jadhav**

Portfolio url: <a href="https://captainaj1.github.io/portfolio/">https://captainaj1.github.io/portfolio/</a>

Mobile: +91 8623947396 Email: aj9145348@gmail.com Country of Citizenship: India

DOB: 08/12/1995

#### **CAREEER SUMMARY**

I have been working as a Web Developer and Video Editor for the past two years. Well versed with Php with working experience in developing web applications in core php, Drupal & WordPress CMS. Also, I have produced a number of videos on YouTube and currently handling multiple channels and Artists on a professional level.

Presently working as a Real Estate Video Editor & Graphics Designer. Aiming to obtain a creative and challenging position as a Non-Linear Video Editor.

### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- Videography, Video Editing, colour correction & colour grading
- Photography, Graphic Designing
- Developing Web applications in Php, Drupal & WordPress CMS
- Adept in software installations & updates
- YouTube SEO

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Editor** – October 2019 to Present

SaudaGhar- Pune, Maharashtra

- Shoot & Edit Property footage, Interviews with customers and leading professionals in the industry, Vlogs and other required videos.
- Producing creative content for YouTube and other social media.
- Producing up to 3 YouTube videos every week, creating daily community posts and designing interactive thumbnails. Producing IGTV videos for Instagram.
- Handling inbound leads and sales part-time.

## Freelance Video Editor – June 2018 to Present

Pune, Maharashtra

- Scheduling video shoots on different locations, arranging camera setup and equipment's.
- Directing and recording videos for different outdoor and indoor setups individually as well as within a team.
- Editing music videos, trailers, Ads, promos, learning videos for different Artists, YouTube channels and social media.
- Managing the YouTube SEO for a couple of channels.

# Web Developer – May 2018 to May 2019

NSoft Technologies Pvt. Ltd- Pune, Maharashtra

- Developing static and dynamic web applications in Drupal and WordPress CMS.
- Writing code in core Php.
- File handling and Database management.
- Front-end customization in HTML/CSS.

## **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS**

## **Bachelors in Computer Engineering (2017)**

Pune University -Pune, India

### SKILLS AND SOFTWARE PROFICIENCY

- Videography, Video Editing, Color correction and Color grading
- Audio Mixing & Synchronization
- Photography, Graphic Designing
- Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, CorelDraw
- Camera Operation: Sony A6000, Sony A7S, Nikon D5200/D5300, Cannon 5D
- Adept in software Installations & updates
- Developing static and dynamic web applications
- Php, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL, Drupal, WordPress
- Social media handling, YouTube SEO

#### **COURSES AND CERTIFICATION**

- ✓ Advanced PHP training at Lavenir Institute of Professional Studies (LIPSINDIA), Pune
- ✓ Programming in Java at NIIT, Pune

### **EXTRA CURRICULAR**

- Trained Musician, proficient in all skin instruments primarily Tabla. Professionally Performing live with Individuals and bands.
- Certification in Tabla from Akhil Bhartiya Gandharva Mahavidyalay, Pune.
- Actively involved in sports, Field Hockey player for School and College.